

SKILLS

Android ABAP (ERP) SQL Github Teamwork Active listening

INTERESTS

- Technology
- Virtual reality
- Robots

Vũ Đình Sơn

Fresher Devlopment

Birth : 29/12/1996

Phone: 0986172912 Mail: sonvudinh96@gmail.com

Address: 33 Phan Huy Ich, Son Trà, Đà Nẵng

OBJECTIVE

Can take care an opportunity and challenging position in your company. With my good background experience in University, old company such as communication skill, teamwork and my own passion for this position. I am committed to contributing to the company be better.

EDUCATION

HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORTATION

From: OCT 2014 - MAY 2018

Major: Information technology - final year with GPA: 2.31/4

EXPERIENCE

GRADUATE TOPIC, COMPANY DOT SOLUTIONS

From: 04/2018 - 06/2018Program language: Java

Job description:

Numbers: 2 people

Purpose: build application detect traffic violations by camera Study OPENCV library (apply for the car licence plate one line).

- Use OpenCV library to process video from camera.
- Draw rectangle and condition to identified picture the cars traffic violation.
- The car picture be cut will go to steps convert color photo to gray photo to binary photo and a few conditions to got license plates.
- After determined the license plates, use Tesseract statement of Test4J library to convert characters to test type.

ERP DEVELOPMENT STAFF, COMPANY FPT INFORMATION SYSTEM HCM

From: 09/2018 - 01/2019

- Program SAP system, ABAP language about report ALV, Smartforms, Excel...
- Training about module MM, CO.
- Write reports modules PA for AEON project.
- Write, Fix and update issue the modules SD, CO, MM, QM...